# **Hung Hao Hsu**

eMail: oscar86hsu@gmail.com

Mobile: +886-981049372

Website: <a href="https://oscarhsu.me">https://oscarhsu.me</a>

### **Profile**

I always have passion about new technologies. Whether it's Cloud Computing, Artificial Intelligence, or Internet Security. Since I was 10, I will sit at the computer science area of the book store and read books about programming, internet, computer system etc.. I enjoy learning and exploring things that make our life more efficient. In the field of cloud services, I have 3 years of hands-on experience on AWS, and worked as a Cloud Engineer for 2 years.

## **Skills**

Tools: Docker, Kubernetes, Github

Knowledge: AWS, Distributed Systems

System: Linux, Unix, Mac OS X, MySQL

**Programming Language:** Python, C/C++, PHP,

HTML/CSS, JavaScript

# Certification

**AWS Certified Solutions Architect – Associate** 

**AWS Certified Developer – Associate** 

**AWS Certified Sysops Administrator – Associate** 

**AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner** 

# **Experience**

**Cloud Development Engineer** at eCloudvalley Digital Technology

Dec 2018 - March 2020

- Built an application that scans for potential security risks, suggestion of high availability on AWS and generated a report that highlight the issues with python.
- Designed loose coupled applications, built microservices and serverless architecture on AWS that saved around 60% of the operation cost.
- Collaborated with product team to develop code, design system and test solutions for our Cloud Management Platform.

### **Cloud Support Engineer** at eCloudvalley Digital Technology

July 2018 - Dec 2018

- Analyzed needs of customers and provide possible solutions, supported customers with technical issues such as scaling their databases automatically and load balancing traffic for their websites.
- Established operating procedure and technical document, which drops the training time of new colleges significantly.

#### **Project Owner** at Racetrack Cloud Services

February 2019 - May 2019

- Identified client's needs and effectively communicated project scope, schedule, and budget, then planned, organize, and implement all aspects of the construction project.
- Built a prototype child toy that can analyze children's behavior while they are playing, and identify possible learning disability at an early age, such as Visual Spatial Perceptual Disorder, Developmental Dyslexia or Specific Learning Disabilities in Mathematics.
- Documented deployment and post deployment procedures.

# **Education**

**Bachelor of Computer Science**. National Chiao Tung University, Taiwan.

**Comprehensive English Program**. New York University, New York.